(Director:)-And who are you?
-I'm her boyfriend.
(Director:)-Isn't she too hot for you?
-A little, yeah.
(Director:)Well, boyfriend, get off my set.
(Penny:)You can't do that.
He's with me.
(Director:)You know what? You can get off
my set, too. You're fired.
(Penny:)What? You can't fire me.
I'm the star.
(Penny:)I'm the girl that goes bananas.
It says so on the poster.
(Director:)Yeah, but we just shot the last scene
where we see your face.
(Director:)So from now own, the star
of the movie is whoever wears this.
(Wil:)Hey, if you're gonna fire her,
then you have to fire me too.
(Wil:)Wow, that fell apart really fast.
(Raj:)Thanks for skipping the movie.
I couldn't sit in that theater
for two hours
(Raj:)wondering about Emily and that guy.
(Sheldon:)Oh, quite all right.
(Sheldon:)After my forehead melanoma scare,
(Sheldon:)I've learned not to sweat
the small stuff.
(Sheldon:)Well, sorry, I don't have all
the ingredients to make chai tea.
(Raj:)-You don't have to make me anything.
-No, I do.